Daffa Putera Kouseina, Mobile Developer

Purwokerto, Indonesia, +6281325218571, kouseinadaffa@gmail.com

LINKS	Portfolio, Github, Youtube, Playstor		
PROFILE	I'm a mobile developer. I have 3 years of experience in mobile development. I have built many Android and iOS with flutter framework. By working on those projects, I accrued an imposing skill set, which has taught me punctuality.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Mar 2024 — Aug 2024	Mobile Developer, PT. Satu V	isi Raya (SAVIR)	Purwokerto
	My technical expertise in Flutter, ena	aya, I played a key role in developing and maintaining m bled me to contribute to the team. I was involved in the to deployment, ensuring high-quality and efficient softv	full software
Jul 2023 — Jul 2024	Mobile Developer, Dealjava		Medan
	methodology - Define git rules, folders, code, etc.	nent process through the entire software life cycle under ogies such as Flutter, Bloc, Stream, Rest Api ooth and wireless	Waterfall
Oct 2021 — May 2023	Mobile Developer, PT. RAK	HASA ARTHA WISESA	Jakarta
	methodology - Define git rules, folders, code, etc Handling playstore, appstore, fireb	ogies such as Flutter, Getx, Firebase, Git, Rest Api, Mid	
Oct 2020 — Nov 2021	Software Engineer, Freelance	(Self employed)	Purwokerto
	- Create app for helps the growth of Health Services for Premature Babies - Create news portal application, who	oremature babies on a regular basis, stores data digitally, s ch contains about digital coins. I online and has 2 applications, namely for ordering and t information around Bandung. I out market in Lampung, with Java	-
EDUCATION			
Oct 2023 — Present	Informatics Engineering, STI	AIK Widya Utama	Purwokerto
SKILLS	Flutter	Git	
	Kotlin	Playstore & Appstore	
	Java	Android & IOS	
HOBBIES	I would like to join tech competition preneur, invofest, etc.	like hackaton or something else. Such as codefest asia, p	ermata youth